teaser-trailer.com 2017-02-21

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for Teaser Trailer  
https://teaser-trailer.com/

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by sending an email to teasertrailermovie [(@)] gmail.com.

For our site (https://teaser-trailer.com/, Teaser Trailer), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by our site and how it is used.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, our site makes use of log files through external partners. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons   
Our site does use cookies (just to check if you visited us in the past). Also be aware that our partners uses cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:  
– Google Adsense  
– Doubleclick  
– Tribal Fusion  
– Infolinks  
– Chitika  
– Goviral

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on our site send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Our site has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our site’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

Google, one of our third-party advertisers, may add a cookie to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. You can choose to opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Links  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Name, Email addresses  
If you provide us with your name and your email (when sending us an email, or posting a comment on the site, in our chat or our forum), be aware that we may collect those data and store them. Keep in mind to be careful not to post your personal data (like emails for example) on public pages.
